# HIKMATULLO MULLAJONOV

## WEB DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

- +998 (94) 602-28-24
- Uzbekistan, Namangan
- https://www.hikmatdev.uz

## **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I have been working in frontend programming since 2019. During this period, I gained experience in creating and developing several web projects. I strive to constantly grow and develop as a developer, keeping up to date with the technological innovations of the day.

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021

# TASHKENT UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

• Computer Engineering

#### ICT IT ACADEMY 2018 - 2019

• Web programming(Frontend)

#### PDP IT ACADEMY 2019 - 2020

• Web programming(Frontend)

# SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap/Ant-design
- Sass
- JavaScript
- ReactJS/Redux
- Git/Github

# LANGUAGES

- Uzbek
- English: Pre-Intermediate
- Russian: B1-B2

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Webstar IT Academy

2022-2023

Frontend Mentor

- Webstar It Learning Center is a company that primarily focuses on improving school-age children's Web programming and computer literacy.
- The following technologies are taught at Webstar: Html, Css, Bootstrap, Sass, JavaScript and React JS.
- This year I tried to increase my experience and to convey my knowledge to my students as fully as possible.

## **Webstar IT Academy**

2023 - PRESENT

Frontend Mentor / Frontend Developer

## Webstar quiz project

- This project is designed for students to take tests at the end of each unit. For example, if the html is completed, one exam test. Test scores are saved and students' practice scores can also be entered. In this way, the test and practice score average can be viewed automatically.
- In this project, I created a convenient design and connected it to the backend. I also created an admin panel section to manage the site.

## Webstar gamification project

- In this project, students complete step-by-step test tasks. For each test they solve, they get a fixed grade based on the section level.
  They can track their history and ratings on their profiles.
- In this project, my task was to create a design that is more interesting for readers and connect to the backend. In this I used react/redux, I chose antd for design.